San Diego | pmtgcode@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/patrick-tu-glynn/

Professional Summary

Junior web developer with a background in music education who has found a way to marry my love for music and programming to create a music experience while using my application. Enjoy working in groups to develop more robust web apps.

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL
- Databases: SQL/mySQL, MongoDB/Mongoose, GQL
- Libraries & Frameworks: React, Bootstrap, Handlebars.js, NPM, PWA, Wordpress, jQuery
- -Stacks & Concepts: OOP, ORM, MVC, MERN
- Servers: Express.js, Apollo
- -Tools: Microsoft Office Suite, Lightroom

EDUCATION

UCSD- Extension | 2022-Present
Concentration: Full Stack Web Developer

Portfolio https://monacoglynn.github.io/react-portfolio/#home

WORK EXPERIENCE

Piano Instructor, Music Pillars | 2022 - Present

Responsibilities: Teaching young students proper technique and theory for playing piano and other keyboard instruments as well as how to play in musical groups with other students.

Piano Instructor, School of Rock Del Mar | 2021 - 2022

Responsibilities: Teaching young students proper technique and theory for playing piano and other keyboard instruments as well as how to play in musical groups with other students.

Private Music Teacher | 2019 - Present

Responsibilities: Private music teacher with 23 years of performance experience in piano, guitar, and mandolin; instructing to students of all ages!

Administrative Assistant & Health Care Enrollment Specialist, J. Glynn & Company | 2006 - Present

Responsibilities: Zoom engineer for large scale virtual healthcare open enrollment events. Perform HIPAA compliant daily clerical/ data entry duties, medical document filing, personal and business enrollments, facilitation & scheduling of online seminars.

Logistics manager, & Keyboardist, Con Brio / 16th & Peralta | 2016 - 2021

Responsibilities: Professional touring keyboardist. General logistics manager; handled scheduling, traveling logistics, lodging, and other administrative back-end tasks.